profootballspot.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy Policy - Forums

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers.

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Cookies**  
This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.

Pro Football Spot knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy covers Pro Football Spot s treatment of personal information that Pro Football Spot gathers when you are on the Pro Football Spot website and when you use Pro Football Spot services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Pro Football Spot does not own or control, or to individuals that Pro Football Spot does not employ or manage.

Information Collected by Pro Football Spot

We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our Pro Football Spot users:

1\. Information You Provide to Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.

2\. Automatic Information: 

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Pro Football Spot and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain "traffic data" on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, ******* cookie information, and the page you requested. Pro Football Spot uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website.  
o Pro Football Spot may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. 

Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While Pro Football Spot will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.

E-mail Communications  
Pro Football Spot is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the "Sharing Your Information" section below. Pro Football Spot may send out e-mails with Pro Football Spot-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.  
Cookies

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. Pro Football Spot cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.

The "help" portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of Pro Football Spot's coolest features. 

Pro Football Spot's advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner Platform-A's privacy policy and opt-out page.

Sharing Your Information 

Rest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below. 

Pro Football Spot Personnel: Pro Football Spot personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of Pro Football Spot business.   
Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if Pro Football Spot or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.

Protection of Pro Football Spot and Others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Pro Football Spot our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Syndication: Pro Football Spot allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the Pro Football Spot website.  
With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.

Children Under 18 Years of Age

You must be 13 years and older to register to use the Pro Football Spot website. As a result, Pro Football Spot does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that Pro Football Spot has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents' permission before using Pro Football Spot or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Pro Football Spot may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Pro Football Spot website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.   
Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit Pro Football Spot website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.   
Effective Date of this Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 10, 2013 and last updated October 10, 2013.
